{
  "apikey": "%PUT-YOUR-API-KEY-HERE%",
  "description": "This is simple calibration data used for testing purposes. Do not use it in production environment!",
  "copyright": "Copyright (C) 2238 by BanAN Technologies Inc.",
  "test-data": [
    {
      "question": "55 + 2",
      "answer": 57
    },
    {
      "question": "79 + 21",
      "answer": 100
    },
    {
      "question": "25 + 20",
      "answer": 45
    },
    {
      "question": "95 + 53",
      "answer": 148
    },
    {
      "question": "13 + 61",
      "answer": 74
    },
    {
      "question": "57 + 36",
      "answer": 93
    },
    {
      "question": "15 + 5",
      "answer": 20
    },
    {
      "question": "80 + 80",
      "answer": 160
    },
    {
      "question": "27 + 63",
      "answer": 90
    },
    {
      "question": "62 + 53",
      "answer": 115
    },
    {
      "question": "21 + 85",
      "answer": 106
    },
    {
      "question": "14 + 60",
      "answer": 74
    },
    {
      "question": "22 + 68",
      "answer": 90
    },
    {
      "question": "83 + 74",
      "answer": 157
    },
    {
      "question": "1 + 80",
      "answer": 81
    },
    {
      "question": "50 + 46",
      "answer": 96
    },
    {
      "question": "98 + 77",
      "answer": 175
    },
    {
      "question": "44 + 60",
      "answer": 104
    },
    {
      "question": "7 + 60",
      "answer": 67
    },
    {
      "question": "94 + 36",
      "answer": 130
    },
    {
      "question": "21 + 14",
      "answer": 35
    },
    {
      "question": "30 + 4",
      "answer": 34
    },
    {
      "question": "19 + 50",
      "answer": 69
    },
    {
      "question": "72 + 45",
      "answer": 117
    },
    {
      "question": "86 + 85",
      "answer": 171
    },
    {
      "question": "33 + 87",
      "answer": 120
    },
    {
      "question": "58 + 17",
      "answer": 75
    },
    {
      "question": "68 + 62",
      "answer": 130
    },
    {
      "question": "79 + 52",
      "answer": 131
    },
    {
      "question": "76 + 5",
      "answer": 81
    },
    {
      "question": "47 + 24",
      "answer": 71
    },
    {
      "question": "23 + 89",
      "answer": 112
    },
    {
      "question": "89 + 40",
      "answer": 129
    },
    {
      "question": "29 + 2",
      "answer": 31
    },
    {
      "question": "2 + 28",
      "answer": 30
    },
    {
      "question": "12 + 79",
      "answer": 91
    },
    {
      "question": "89 + 68",
      "answer": 157
    },
    {
      "question": "43 + 74",
      "answer": 117
    },
    {
      "question": "76 + 33",
      "answer": 109
    },
    {
      "question": "65 + 4",
      "answer": 69
    },
    {
      "question": "94 + 87",
      "answer": 181
    },
    {
      "question": "90 + 30",
      "answer": 120
    },
    {
      "question": "71 + 99",
      "answer": 170
    },
    {
      "question": "40 + 38",
      "answer": 78
    },
    {
      "question": "9 + 80",
      "answer": 89
    },
    {
      "question": "93 + 32",
      "answer": 125
    },
    {
      "question": "39 + 24",
      "answer": 63
    },
    {
      "question": "93 + 4",
      "answer": 97
    },
    {
      "question": "8 + 1",
      "answer": 9
    },
    {
      "question": "76 + 61",
      "answer": 137
    },
    {
      "question": "68 + 24",
      "answer": 92
    },
    {
      "question": "42 + 57",
      "answer": 99
    },
    {
      "question": "31 + 53",
      "answer": 84
    },
    {
      "question": "84 + 53",
      "answer": 137
    },
    {
      "question": "92 + 40",
      "answer": 132
    },
    {
      "question": "33 + 8",
      "answer": 41
    },
    {
      "question": "78 + 49",
      "answer": 127
    },
    {
      "question": "3 + 94",
      "answer": 97
    },
    {
      "question": "61 + 89",
      "answer": 150
    },
    {
      "question": "34 + 62",
      "answer": 96
    },
    {
      "question": "78 + 28",
      "answer": 106
    },
    {
      "question": "84 + 1",
      "answer": 85
    },
    {
      "question": "28 + 16",
      "answer": 44
    },
    {
      "question": "26 + 6",
      "answer": 32
    },
    {
      "question": "85 + 85",
      "answer": 170
    },
    {
      "question": "83 + 2",
      "answer": 85
    },
    {
      "question": "80 + 93",
      "answer": 173
    },
    {
      "question": "77 + 99",
      "answer": 176
    },
    {
      "question": "92 + 55",
      "answer": 147
    },
    {
      "question": "37 + 30",
      "answer": 67
    },
    {
      "question": "41 + 50",
      "answer": 91
    },
    {
      "question": "47 + 22",
      "answer": 69
    },
    {
      "question": "86 + 93",
      "answer": 179
    },
    {
      "question": "72 + 35",
      "answer": 107
    },
    {
      "question": "51 + 21",
      "answer": 72
    },
    {
      "question": "8 + 60",
      "answer": 68
    },
    {
      "question": "6 + 22",
      "answer": 28
    },
    {
      "question": "53 + 45",
      "answer": 98
    },
    {
      "question": "25 + 49",
      "answer": 74
    },
    {
      "question": "98 + 27",
      "answer": 125
    },
    {
      "question": "78 + 100",
      "answer": 178
    },
    {
      "question": "4 + 80",
      "answer": 84
    },
    {
      "question": "52 + 41",
      "answer": 93
    },
    {
      "question": "79 + 91",
      "answer": 170
    },
    {
      "question": "72 + 6",
      "answer": 78
    },
    {
      "question": "55 + 88",
      "answer": 143
    },
    {
      "question": "75 + 37",
      "answer": 112
    },
    {
      "question": "9 + 94",
      "answer": 103
    },
    {
      "question": "67 + 55",
      "answer": 122
    },
    {
      "question": "34 + 47",
      "answer": 81
    },
    {
      "question": "27 + 54",
      "answer": 81
    },
    {
      "question": "15 + 94",
      "answer": 109
    },
    {
      "question": "26 + 69",
      "answer": 95
    },
    {
      "question": "67 + 9",
      "answer": 76
    },
    {
      "question": "87 + 10",
      "answer": 97
    },
    {
      "question": "52 + 62",
      "answer": 114
    },
    {
      "question": "28 + 39",
      "answer": 67
    },
    {
      "question": "49 + 75",
      "answer": 124
    },
    {
      "question": "31 + 81",
      "answer": 112
    },
    {
      "question": "47 + 88",
      "answer": 135
    }
  ],
  "chunk": {
    "number": 13,
    "total": 22,
    "size": 100,
    "range": {
      "from": 1200,
      "to": 1300
    }
  }
}